faketaxi.xxx 2017-01-06

# Privacy Policy | Fake Taxi XXX

**Privacy Policy**

What information do we collect?  
We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
